Office of Alumni Relations Records UA011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and audio-visual material, 1850 -- 2015; 1956 -- 1997; UA011.004; 3.95 Linear Feet; 27 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - Audio Cassette:Rick Hauck speech, 1985-02-19; UA011.004.048.00015 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Tufts University NY Alumni - Jean Mayer and John Hammock, UA011.004.048.00016 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Televisions greatest hits, 1970 -- 1989; UA011.004.048.00017 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: The Boston Ballet, season preview, 1990 -- 1991; UA011.004.048.00018 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Tufts in Song, 1990; UA011.004.049.00001 (Reel 49)
  - Audio Cassette: Tufts in Song, UA011.004.049.00002 (Reel 49)
  - Audio Cassette: "Tufts Songs", TU Chorus, 1956; UA011.004.049.00003 (Reel 49)
  - Tufts in Song Folder, UA011.004.049.00004 (Box 14)
  - Photographs, 1960 -- 1980; UA011.004.055.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. Poster 1: Five Photographs Photograph 1: Campus Art Photograph 2: Uncaptioned [man working on early computer] Photograph 3: Uncaptioned [woman doing art projects with four young children] Photograph 4: Uncaptioned [seven people in a (budget?) meeting] Photograph 5: Dr. C. Stuart Welch, left, co-chairman of the Equipment Fund Campaign, listens attentively to Dr. William E. Browne, vice-president of the Medical Alumni Association. On the right is Harry Blotner, Medical Alumni Secretary-Treasurer.
  - Photographs, 1960 -- 1970; UA011.004.055.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. Poster 2: Five Photographs Photograph 1: WGBH-FM "Massachusetts Viewpoint" November 20, 1963 [Photo includes Sen. Edward Kennedy] Photograph 2: Uncaptioned [man making a toast/speech] Photograph 3: Rick Linde Photograph 4: Uncaptioned [Six women meeting] Photograph 5: Uncaptioned [Fletcher Dorm (Blakeley Hall)]
  - Photographs, 1976 -- 1978; UA011.004.055.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. Poster 3: Three Photographs Photograph 1: Arena Theater-"Tobacco Road" Photograph 2: Dean Bernard Harleston Parents Weekend 1976 Photograph 3: Arena Theater-"Tobacco Road"
  - Photographs, 1960 -- 1980; UA011.004.055.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. Poster 4: Five Photographs Photograph 1: Blizzard 1978 Photograph 2: Final Exams 1975 Photograph 3: Snow Storm, February, 1978 Photograph 4: Uncaptioned [Woman speaker] Photograph 5: Uncaptioned [Swimmer]
  - Photographs, 1960 -- 1970; UA011.004.055.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. Poster 5: Five Photographs Photograph 1: Reading Seminars Photograph 2: Uncaptioned [Five students and one adult standing from of sign for the North hall school] Photograph 3: Uncaptioned [Students on bleachers] Photograph 4: Uncaptioned [Ten men in lecture hall (automobile lecture?)] Photograph 5: Class of 1921 [possibly 1971, 50th reunion]
  - Photographs, 1970 -- 1980; UA011.004.055.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. Poster 6: Four Photographs Photograph 1: Uncaptioned [Belly-dancing class] Photograph 2: Uncaptioned [Two players in Tufts v. Rhode Island soccer game] Photograph 3: Class on Consumer Products Evaluation Photograph 4: Sigma Nu Dance Marathon-1979
  - Photographs, 1910 -- 1950; UA011.004.056.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. CAPTIONS: Poster 7: Nine Photographs (left to right, then top to bottom) Photograph 1: Civil Engineering students doing what they have always done. Note their stocking caps. Probably taken in the 1920s. Photograph 2: A Tufts Arena Theatre production circa 1940. Tall man in left center is the late John Holmes, A29, who wrote "Along the Row." [text written below the photograph: "Photos by Roger Whittmore (?)" and "Scene from 'The Male Animal'".] Photograph 3: What appears to be rugby matches on the Oval, probably taken in the early 1900's [sic]. Note Metcalf Hall (with Tower!) in center background and old Jackson Gym on extreme left. Photograph 4: The Kursaal, so named by the late President Carmichael. Located in Cousens Gym across the corridor from the current Athletics Office, it was equivalent in the late thirties and early forties to the Curtis Hall snack bar. Photograph 5: Commencement procession, probably in the early forties. Photograph 6: Track team, probably taken in the early 1940's. Coach "Ding" Dussault on left. Fellow next to him in striped jersey died overseas in World War II. Photograph 7: Physical education classes - but when? Possibly the twenties or the thirties. Photograph 8: Opera production probably staged in the old Goddard Gym, now the Fletcher School building. Photograph 9: ROTC cadets on parade during WWII. The officer is Clarence P. Houston, WWI decorated officer, Director of Athletics at Tufts for many years, Professor of Business Law and first Vice President for Development (now called Resources). He was in charge of their military training on campus. He built Alumni House as his home
  - Photographs, 1920 -- 1940; UA011.004.056.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. CAPTIONS: Poster 8: Four Photographs (left to right, then top to bottom) Photograph 1: Goddard Gym was built in 1883. The Fletcher School opened in 1932. Between these two dates all indoor physical education was carried on in this building. [first caption] Goddard Hall-Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy-Old Gymnasium. [second caption]. Photograph 2: Members of the faculty and administration, probably taken in the 1930s. Man at the extreme right is Professor Munro, who took thousands of photographs of the campus. (image in the DL-MS036:MS036.011.DO.01198) Photograph 3: Uncaptioned [Professor Leo Rich Lewis and unidentified man in fur coat] Photograph 4: Professor Leo Rich Lewis, composer of "Dear Alma Mater", at his desk. Well known eccentricity - filing everything on tiny scraps of paper in the numerous cubbyholes in his desk. (image in DL-MS036:MS036.011.DO.01136)
  - Photographs, 1850 -- 1920; UA011.004.057.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. CAPTIONS: Poster 9: Nine Photographs (left to right, then top to bottom) Photograph 1: 1959 Row of Trees. Only five years after the college opened! Photograph 2: Locomotive stopped for some obscure reason in gut along Boston Avenue. Note old-style police helmet on officer standing on locomotive steps on extreme left of picture. Photograph 3: Packard Hall 30 years after it was built. [Caption on photograph reads "Daniel Pratt at Tufts College in May, 1885"] (image in DL- UA136.002.DO.04676) Photograph 4: The old bell on the roof of Ballou Hall. It was used for all kinds of signaling purposes. (image in DL- MS054.003.DO.02459) Photograph 5: The Tufts campus in the earliest years. Note the reservoir on the right. The houses at the left face Professors Row and Curtis Street. The road in the foreground is Packard Avenue. Photograph 6: Photo taken from where Wessell Library now stands with Boston in the background. Photograph 7: Goddard Chapel with 1959 row of trees. Many trees were planted on the Tufts campus over the years. Many of these were destroyed in the 1938 hurricane. Photograph 8: Photo taken from where Mugar Hall now stands with Boston in the background. The white house (left center) is now Zeta Psi. Photograph 9: Men's singing group taken in the old Goddard Gymnasium (now the Fletcher School). Those beams are now hidden from sight unless you know what door to open to see a portion of them. Note gym apparatus in background. Photo taken in the 1920's [sic] or earlier.
  - Photographs, 1920 -- 1950; UA011.004.057.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    These dates are approximate. Some of these images may be in the Digital Library. This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. It is an oversize poster with pasted photographs of various Tufts people and activities, some are captioned, some are not. CAPTIONS: Poster 10: Eight Photographs (left to right, then top to bottom) Photograph 1: No Alumni Day for many years (up to the early 1940's) was ever complete without the presence of the Salem Cadet Band. One can get an idea of when this photo was taken by the car on the left. Photograph 2: The campus lawn was decorated with Japanese lanterns for Alumni Day. The Salem Cadet Band plays on the platform. Photograph 3: Probably Boston Red Sox Players in the early forties dropping pennies into Jumbos trunk for luck. The Red Sox for many years took early spring practice in Cousens Gym. Photograph 4: Alumni Day photo. The band was probably an authentic Navy band. Photo probably taken in the early 1920's. Photograph 5: The Alumni Day Luncheon on the campus lawn served under a huge tent. Most recent class identifiable is 1936. Probably taken in 1937. Photograph 6: Jumbo's preserved hide needed constant care. Every five or six years experts carefully worked on it to keep it from disintegrating. Photograph 7: Costumed members of the class of 1917 at an Alumni Day, perhaps in 1932. Photograph 8: Though only the stuffed remains of a once magnificent beast, Tufts' own Jumbo was loved not only by Tufts folks, but by school children who came to see him for miles around. This photo, probably taken in the late thirties, not only shows the size of Jumbo, but other stuffed animals in the background. Barnum at one time contained a large number of stuffed creatures, both animals and birds.
  - Kick-off dinner Tufts second century fund, photograph, 1910 -- 1950; UA011.004.058.00001 (Box Shared 38)
    This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in Winter 2009. Note the box number. This item is housed in a box with other oversized items.
  - Kick-off dinner Tufts second century fund, copper picture plate, 1910 -- 1950; UA011.004.058.00002 (Box Shared 38)
    Copper picture plate, slightly scrateched. This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in Winter 2009. Note the box number. This item is housed with other oversized items.
- Photo Albums, 1995; UA011.005; 1.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains photo albums.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Photo album, UA011.005.050.001 (Box 50)
  - Photo album, UA011.005.051.001 (Box 51)
- Tufts University Office of Alumni Relations, Tufts Clubs, 1960 -- 1999; UA011.006; 1.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains records relating to the Tufts Clubs (alumni networks) in national and international locations.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by Club location.
  - Tufts Club: Albany, NY, 1977; UA011.006.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Argentina, 1995; UA011.006.052.00002 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Atlanta, 1994 -- 1995; UA011.006.052.00003 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Baltimore, 1993 -- 1995; UA011.006.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Boston, 1993 -- 1994; UA011.006.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Boston, 1960; UA011.006.052.00006 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Boston (North Shore), UA011.006.052.00007 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Boston (South Shore), UA011.006.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Brazil, 1995; UA011.006.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: British, 1994; UA011.006.052.00010 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Chicago, 1994 -- 1997; UA011.006.052.00011 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1962 -- 1990; UA011.006.052.00012 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1962 -- 1990; UA011.006.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1991 -- 1995; UA011.006.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1991 -- 1995; UA011.006.052.00015 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1993 -- 1997; UA011.006.052.00016 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1995 -- 1999; UA011.006.052.00017 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, 1995 -- 1999; UA011.006.052.00018 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Club: Cape Cod, handbook for officers, UA011.006.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: Cleveland, UA011.006.053.00002 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: Colorado, UA011.006.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: Connecticut, 1994 -- 1996; UA011.006.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: France, UA011.006.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: Germany, UA011.006.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: Greece, 1994 -- 1995; UA011.006.053.00007 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club: Hong Kong, 1996 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Honolulu, UA011.006.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Houston, 1993 -- 1995; UA011.006.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Kansas City, 1994 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00012 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Japan, 1997; UA011.006.053.00013 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Long Island, 1996; UA011.006.053.00014 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Minnesota, 1997; UA011.006.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Minneapolis, 1996; UA011.006.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Los Angeles, 1993 -- 1996; UA011.006.053.00017 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Maine, UA011.006.053.00018 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Miami, 1996 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00019 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Neponset Valley, 1993 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00020 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, New Hampshire, 1993 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00021 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, New York, 1993 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00022 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Northern Ohio, 1997; UA011.006.053.00023 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, North Carolina, 1995 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00024 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Oregon, 1993; UA011.006.053.00025 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Palm Beach, UA011.006.053.00026 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Rhode Island, 1993 -- 1995; UA011.006.053.00027 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Rochester, 1994; UA011.006.053.00028 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Seattle, UA011.006.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, San Diego, UA011.006.053.00030 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, San Francisco, 1993 -- 1996; UA011.006.053.00031 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Spain, 1995; UA011.006.053.00032 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Spain, 1996; UA011.006.053.00033 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Switzerland, 1997; UA011.006.053.00034 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Tokyo, UA011.006.053.00035 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, Washington, D.C., 1993 -- 1997; UA011.006.053.00036 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Club, West Florida, UA011.006.053.00037 (Box 53)
- Tufts University Office of Alumni Relations, subject files., 1957 -- 2002; UA011.007; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains subject files from the Tufts University Office of Alumni Relations.
  - TOAR: subject files, 1958 -- 1959; UA011.007.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: 10 most memorable moments at Tufts, 1998; UA011.007.054.00002 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: subject files, 1959 -- 1989; UA011.007.054.00003 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Alumni Council member directory, 2000; UA011.007.054.00004 (Box 54)
  - Training conference for field representatives, 1966; UA011.007.054.00005 (Box 54)
  - Misc. groups, UA011.007.054.00006 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: postcards, UA011.007.054.00007 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Handbook for Tufts Club officers, 1957; UA011.007.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Handbook for reunion committees, 1957; UA011.007.054.00009 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Medical alumni relations, 1980 -- 1982; UA011.007.054.00010 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Dental alumni relations, 1980 -- 1981; UA011.007.054.00011 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: correspondence, 1980; UA011.007.054.00012 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Class of 1959, 30th reunion review, 1989; UA011.007.054.00013 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Oral history project, 2002; UA011.007.054.00014 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Medford Historical Society, 1993; UA011.007.054.00015 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: School of Veterinary Medicine, 1987 -- 1994; UA011.007.054.00016 (Box 54)
  - TOAR: Alumni college abroad, 1995; UA011.007.054.00017 (Box 54)
- Tufts University Office of Alumni Relations, give-aways, 1941 -- 2002; UA011.008; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains items given at Alumni events including frisbees, pens and key chains.
  - Alumni Day button, 1941-06-14; UA011.008.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Frisbee, 2002; UA011.008.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - Notebook and pen, 2002; UA011.008.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - Lanyard, 2002; UA011.008.067.00004 (Box 67)
- Secretary of Alumni Assocation, Fred Nickless, 1950 -- 1987; 1967 -- 1984; UA011.009; 8.9 Linear Feet
  This series contains the files of the alumni secretary (now called director) of the Tufts University Alumni Association, Fred P. Nickless, files contain symposium pamphlets, correspondence files, committee files, some death reports of alumni, and a few alumni committee handbooks. This series contains alumni symposium pamphlets for 1967 and 1969, various committee files, the chronological correspondence files from 1971 to 1984, and the correspondences of the alumni office staff. These include the Sheetz and Tredennick correspondences. There are alumni committee handbooks and death reports of alumni in 1976 which are restricted. Fred Nickless took these files home from the alumni office upon his retirement in 1986; his daughter returned them in 2007 to the university.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - [Alumni Leaders Symposium ], 1967; UA011.009.058.00001 (Box 58)
  - [Alumni Leaders Symposium], 1969; UA011.009.058.00002 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Council Committee Meeting], 1975; UA011.009.058.00003 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Alumni Activity Committee], 1962 -- 1963; UA011.009.058.00004 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Campus Committee], 1963; UA011.009.058.00005 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Chair Committee], 1965; UA011.009.058.00006 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Colors Committee], 1950 -- 1960; UA011.009.058.00007 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Committee- Alumni Living Distance from Campus], 1973; UA011.009.058.00008 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Committees], 1969 -- 1971; UA011.009.058.00009 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Committee Alumni Seminars], 1969 -- 1971; UA011.009.058.00010 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Committee on the Council], 1975; UA011.009.058.00011 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Departmental Committee], 1961 -- 1967; UA011.009.058.00012 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Education Study Commission], 1960 -- 1972; UA011.009.058.00013 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Inn Study Committee], 1960 -- 1961; UA011.009.058.00014 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Library Committee], 1966 -- 1967; UA011.009.058.00015 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Photos Committee], 1965 -- 1966; UA011.009.058.00016 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Planning Committee], 1960 -- 1963; UA011.009.058.00017 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Publications Committee], 1955 -- 1968; UA011.009.058.00018 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Spare Committee], 1958 -- 1965; UA011.009.058.00019 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Student Relations Committee], 1958; UA011.009.058.00020 (Box 58)
  - [Ad Hoc Tufts Alumni Association], 1972; UA011.009.058.00021 (Box 58)
  - [Alumni Leaders Symposium], 1967; UA011.009.058.00022 (Box 58)
  - [Committee Assignment], 1971 -- 1979; UA011.009.058.00023 (Box 58)
  - [Committee on Council of Young Alumni], 1962 -- 1963; UA011.009.058.00024 (Box 58)
  - [Concert Program Committee], 1974; UA011.009.058.00025 (Box 58)
  - [Lists], 1967 -- 1978; UA011.009.058.00026 (Box 58)
  - [Membership Resources], 1971; UA011.009.058.00027 (Box 58)
  - [Miscellaneous], 1962 -- 1973; UA011.009.058.00028 (Box 58)
  - [Presidents Duties], 1966; UA011.009.058.00029 (Box 58)
  - [President TUAA], UA011.009.058.00030 (Box 58)
    Date unknown
  - [Publications Committee], 1977 -- 1978; UA011.009.058.00031 (Box 58)
  - [Role Duality of Officers, sub-committee], 1971; UA011.009.058.00032 (Box 58)
  - [Self Study Ad Hoc Committee], 1966 -- 1967; UA011.009.058.00033 (Box 58)
  - [Sub-Committee on Ind. Alumni Association], 1970 -- 1971; UA011.009.058.00034 (Box 58)
  - [Sub-Committee on Faculty Recognition], 1970; UA011.009.058.00035 (Box 58)
  - TAC sub-com. on nom. com. procedures, 1970 -- 1971; UA011.009.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - TAC sub-com. on srs. award recips, 1969 -- 1979; UA011.009.059.00002 (Box 59)
  - TAC sub-com. on role of Tufts alum., 1971 -- 1979; UA011.009.059.00003 (Box 59)
  - TAC-special events, 1958 -- 1965; UA011.009.059.00004 (Box 59)
  - Ad hoc theater committee, 1963 -- 1968; UA011.009.059.00005 (Box 59)
  - TAV-Tufts club loan committee, 1960; UA011.009.059.00006 (Box 59)
  - TUAA-by-laws, 1960 -- 1973; UA011.009.059.00007 (Box 59)
  - T. Univ. alum. assn. 1/2, 1969 -- 1972; UA011.009.059.00008 (Box 59)
  - T Univ. alum assn. 2/2, 1960 -- 1970; UA011.009.059.00009 (Box 59)
  - TU-trustees, 1970; UA011.009.059.00010 (Box 59)
  - Trustees study committee Vice President Tredinnicks's file 1/2, 1968 -- 1969; UA011.009.059.00011 (Box 59)
  - Trustees study committee Vice President Tredinnicks's file 2/2, 1968 -- 1969; UA011.009.059.00012 (Box 59)
  - TAC members emeriti, 1974; UA011.009.059.00013 (Box 59)
  - TAC agendas/notices, 1963 -- 1972; UA011.009.059.00014 (Box 59)
  - TAC general, 1962 -- 1970; UA011.009.059.00015 (Box 59)
  - Amendment of acts of sec. 1 of ch. 141 of 1852, 1970; UA011.009.059.00016 (Box 59)
  - Chronological file, 1971; UA011.009.059.00017 (Box 59)
  - Chronological file, 1971; UA011.009.059.00018 (Box 59)
  - Chronological file, 1971; UA011.009.059.00019 (Box 59)
  - Chronological file, 1971 -- 1972; UA011.009.059.00020 (Box 59)
  - Chronological file, 1972; UA011.009.060.00001 (Box 60)
  - Chronological file, 1972; UA011.009.060.00002 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1972 -- 1973; UA011.009.060.00003 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1973; UA011.009.060.00004 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1973; UA011.009.060.00005 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1973; UA011.009.060.00006 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1073 -- 1973; UA011.009.060.00007 (Box 60)